{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Ceramic \u0026 Porcelain Tile Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40037/":{"taskOID":40037,"originalTaskOID":40037,"setID":361,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6236,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6237,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the tile for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8270,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8269,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6238,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Tile Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the tile be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8271,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8272,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8273,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tub/Shower","answerDisplayText":"Tub/Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8274,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8275,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6239,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Tile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of tile do you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Glazed ceramic tile","answerDisplayText":"Glazed ceramic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special or custom tile","answerDisplayText":"Special or custom tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8279,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8280,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8281,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6241,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area to be tiled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8283,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 25 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 25 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8284,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"25-150 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"25-150 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 150 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 150 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6242,"questionDisplayText":"Borders","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want any special borders or patterns?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8286,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8287,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6236,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6237,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the tile for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8270,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8269,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8270,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8269,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6238,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Tile Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the tile be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8271,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8272,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8273,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tub/Shower","answerDisplayText":"Tub/Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8274,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8275,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8271,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8272,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8273,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tub/Shower","answerDisplayText":"Tub/Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8274,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8275,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6239,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Tile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of tile do you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Glazed ceramic tile","answerDisplayText":"Glazed ceramic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special or custom tile","answerDisplayText":"Special or custom tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8279,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8280,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8281,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Glazed ceramic tile","answerDisplayText":"Glazed ceramic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special or custom tile","answerDisplayText":"Special or custom tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8279,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8280,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8281,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6241,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area to be tiled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8283,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 25 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 25 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8284,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"25-150 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"25-150 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 150 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 150 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8283,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 25 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 25 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8284,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"25-150 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"25-150 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 150 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 150 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6242,"questionDisplayText":"Borders","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want any special borders or patterns?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8286,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8287,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8286,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8287,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40037/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40037,"taskName":"Tile: Ceramic and Porcelain - Install","taskDescription":"Install Ceramic or Porcelain Tile","xmTaskDescriptor":"Ceramic \u0026 Porcelain Tile Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":389,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"ceramic marble counter slate quartz","textMessagingName":"Inst Ceramic Tile","rolloverLongDesc":"Installation or complete replacement of either ceramic or stone tile on bars, countertops, vanities, mantels, hearths, walls \u0026 floors. Includes small mosaic tiles mounted on a fabric mesh all the way up to 24 inch square tiles.","rolloverShortDesc":"Install new or replace tile on floors, countertops, walls \u0026 showers, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Ceramic or Porcelain Tile.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Ceramic Tile Flooring Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Porcelain Tile Installers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Ceramic \u0026 Porcelain Tile Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tile: Ceramic and Porcelain - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Ceramic and Porcelain Tile Project","urlName":"Tile-Ceramic-and-Porcelain-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Ceramic Tile Flooring Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"ceramic,porcelain","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":361,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}